whereivebeen.com 2010-05-03

# Where I've Been

The following Privacy Policy summarizes the various ways that we use the information you provide to us or we gather from you while you use the whereivebeen.com online service (the "Service"), as provided by Where I've Been, LLC (the "Service Provider" or "us" or "we"), at www.whereivebeen.com ("WIB" or the "Site"). It is our goal to provide you with information that is tailored to your individual needs and, at the same time, protect your privacy.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. Your use of any part of the Service will constitute your agreement to this Privacy Policy. If you cannot agree with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Service. This Privacy Policy does not cover information collected elsewhere, including, without limitation, offline or on sites linked to through the Service.

In addition to reviewing this Privacy Policy, please read our Terms and Conditions. Your use of the Service constitutes agreement to the Terms and Conditions as well.

This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time; the date of the most recent revisions will appear on this page, so check back often. Continued use of the Service by you will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to the Privacy Policy.

### What Information We Collect from You

When you register with WIB, we ask for the basics including your name, email address, and password and allow you to provide us with other information, including your travel information and preferences.

For all WIB visitors, not just registered users, we collect information such as IP address, browser type, domain name, access times, duration of visit, referring URL, platform, new and repeat information, time stamp, and exit page information.

If you contact us, we also will collect the information you provide that details the nature of your question or problem to enhance the quality of our Service.

### What Organization Is Collecting the Information

Where I've Been, LLC operates and manages www.whereivebeen.com. More information about us may be found at About Us.

### How Your Information Is Protected

We maintain data handling and storage practices and procedures that are designed to ensure the integrity and confidentiality of user information. Current Internet security methods and technologies are used to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure correct use of information.

### When We May Share Your Information

The information we gather is used to create and maintain your travel itineraries and your travel profile and to send you marketing messages. We also use the information that we gather to target content on our Site to more closely match your interests and target email marketing messages that are more appropriate to your needs.

When you use the Service, the personal information you provide may be shared with third parties for access to such information including your friends, relatives and business associates. The third parties may also be permitted to edit the information you have provided to us and to designate others to access and edit such information.

Certain portions of the personal information you provide to us also may be displayed in your public profile.

In addition, we may share your personal information as follows: 

  * When we believe it is appropriate to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal or suspected illegal activities; to protect and defend the rights, property, or safety of WIB, our users ,or others; and in connection with the enforcement of our Terms and Conditions.
  * In connection with a corporate transaction, such as a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy.
  * With business firms contracted to provide specific services to us, in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy. In situations such as this where your data is shared with a third-party firm, the firm will be contractually obligated to use your personal data only for the purpose for which our relationship with the firm exists. The firm will not have the right to share your data with other organizations or contact you outside the bounds of their contract with us.
  * If we have a good faith belief that we are required to do so by law or legal process, to respond to claims, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Service Provider or others. This includes, but is not limited to, fraud, technical malfunctions or abuse of our network or systems. We also may provide user information to third parties for the purpose of resolving disputes that arise in the normal course of business.

From time to time, we also may share general statistical information about our Site and visitors such as the number of visitors, aggregate ,and non-personally identifiable demographic data, etc., with our advertisers and partners.

### What Choices Are Available to You

Registration is optional. If you choose not to register, certain features of the Service and sections of our Site may be inaccessible, but you will be able view the main pages of the Site.

In the "My Account" section of the Site, you may make changes to your account and change your email address, password, or contact information. You may also subscribe or unsubscribe for communications from us. Registration and login are required to access these account settings.

As we explain in more detail below, we use cookies to improve your experience with our service and reduce the time it takes for you to prepare an itinerary. You may choose not to receive a cookie file by enabling your Web browser to refuse cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie. Please be aware, however, that by refusing to accept cookies, you will be unable to access a significant portion of the Site.

### Email Communication You Receive from Us

As well as emails confirming registration, emails that include information about your account, and emails relating directly to an itinerary or travel profile created through the Service, unless you unsubscribe, we may send you emails containing information we believe will be of use and interest to you. For example: 

  * We will update you on any important functionality changes to our Service via email.
  * We will keep you informed about WIB promotions, sweepstakes, programs, etc., and other special offers that we think you will find valuable.

If you decide that you are no longer interested in receiving communications from us, you have several choices for opting out of future mailings: 

  * You may follow the instructions in our emails on how to unsubscribe yourself from our email list.
  * You may click on "My Account" at the top of any page on our Site and update your Email Subscription settings.

### Cookies

A cookie is a unique identifier sent to your computer by a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie lets a computer server identify your computer. A cookie is what allows many sites to greet you upon every return with a personalized message even before you actively login. We use cookies to improve your user experience and reduce the time it takes for you to create an itinerary. Our cookies do not include any sensitive information, but they do help us track which of our Web pages are visited and what services are most often used. Please note that in order to use our Site, your Web browser must be configured to accept cookies.

### Third-Party Advertising

From time to time, we may use a third-party advertising company to serve advertising on our behalf. Through the use of technology devices commonly referred to as cookies and action tags, this third-party ad-serving company can measure the effectiveness of our ads. We do not have access to the third-party company's cookies, which are similar to our own cookies. The company employs an action tag (also known as a Web Beacon or a one-pixel .gif file) to set or read cookies. Our third-party ad server may also receive specific information about your use of the Service. Rest assured that this shared information is anonymous and does not contain any sensitive information. The company may use information about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

### Frontier Airlines, Terms and Conditions

Win free round trip tickets from Frontier Airlines! 

Must be 21 to enter. Winners will be notified via email on or before November 5, 2009. One (1) Grand Prize winner will be awarded two (2) Frontier Airlines Classic round trip tickets, to be redeemed to any Frontier Airlines destination in the 48 contiguous United States, between December 1, 2009 and December 15, 2010 (*blackout dates apply). 

By entering this Contest, you will be automatically opted-in to receive communications from Frontier Airlines and may opt out upon receiving the first communication. Read below for complete terms and conditions.

*The Blackout Dates for 2009 are Dec. 18 - 19, 22 - 23, 26 – 29. 2010: Jan. 1 – 5, 15 -16, and 18; Feb. 12, 13, and 15, March 5-7, 11-14, 20, 21, 25 – 28; April 1 – 5, 10, 11; May 27 – 29, and 31; June 25 – 27; July 1 – 5, 10, 11; Sept. 3, 4, 6; Nov. 18 – 30; Dec. 16 – 31.  

Official Contest Rules  

NO PURCHASE OR PAYMENT OF ANY KIND IS NECESSARY TO ENTER OR WIN THIS CONTEST. PURCHASE WILL NOT INCREASE YOUR CHANCES OF WINNING. 

ELIGIBILITY. The “Which Frontier Animal Are You?” Contest is open to all legal residents of the United States who are (a) 21 years of age or older at the time of entry. Employees and their immediate families (spouses, parents, children and siblings and their respective spouses) of Appssavvy, Inc., Where I've Been, and Frontier Airlines, Inc., and each of their respective parent companies, sponsors, affiliates, distributors, subsidiaries, and advertising/promotion agencies and/or those living in the same household of each such employee are not eligible. Subject to all applicable federal, state, provincial, and local laws and regulations. Void in Puerto Rico and where prohibited by law.

SPONSOR. The Contest is sponsored by Frontier Airlines, Inc., 7001 Tower Road, Denver, CO 80249 ("Sponsor").

AGREEMENT TO OFFICIAL RULES. Participation in the Contest constitutes entrant's full and unconditional agreement to and acceptance of these Official Rules and the decisions of Sponsor, which are final and binding.

CONTEST PERIOD. The Contest begins on September 30, 2009 at 12:01 p.m. Mountain Daylight Time ("MDT") and will end on October 30, 2009 at 12:01 a.m. Sponsor's computer is the official time keeping device for the Contest.

ENTRY   
Contest Period. During the Contest Period , go to www.WhereIveBeen.com and follow the instructions to take the quiz “Which Frontier Animal Are You?” Upon receipt of the quiz results, you may enter your e-mail address to enter to win the Grand Prize. Upon successful submission of an e-mail address, you will automatically be entered for one (1) entry into the Contest drawing.

LIMITS  
Each participant may enter the Contest one (1) time during the Qualifying Period. Any attempt by any participant to submit more than one entry will result in immediate disqualification of the participant. Sponsor and the Released Parties (defined below) are not responsible for: lost, incomplete, illegible, late, or misdirected entries; any error, omission, interruption, defect or delay in transmission or communication; technical or mechanical malfunctions; failures or malfunctions of phones, phone lines, or telephone systems; interrupted or unavailable cable or satellite systems; errors in these Official Rules, in any Contest-related advertisements or other materials; failures of electronic equipment, computer hardware or software; or inaccurate entry information, whether caused by equipment, programming used in this Contest, human processing error, or otherwise. In the event Sponsor determines that the Contest is compromised by causes beyond its reasonable control, Sponsor reserves the right to suspend, modify or terminate the Contest at any time. All entries will be deemed to have been submitted by the owner of the email account from which they were submitted. For theses purposes, an email account holder shall mean the natural person assigned to such email account by the Internet access provider, online service provider or other organization responsible for assigning email addresses for the domain associated with such email account. Sponsor reserves the right to verify email addresses and to disqualify persons Sponsor determines have abused any aspect of this Promotion. Sponsor reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to void any and all entries of an entrant who Sponsor believes has attempted to tamper with or impair the administration, security, fairness, or proper play of this Contest. In the event Sponsor determines that the Contest is compromised by causes beyond its reasonable control, Sponsor reserves the right to suspend, modify or terminate the Contest.  

VERIFICATION OF POTENTIAL WINNERS. The potential winners must comply with all terms and conditions of these Official Rules to win. Except where prohibited, a potential winner of prizes must sign and return to Sponsor, within ten (10) days of the date that notice or attempted notice is sent by Sponsor, an affidavit of eligibility, a fully completed IRS Form W-9, and a liability/publicity release, in order to claim his/her prize. Travel companion(s) must be 18 years of age or older at the time any trip is taken to accompany winner on any trips and except where prohibited, must also sign and return an affidavit of eligibility and a liability/publicity release prior to travel. Winners or travel companions who are Tennessee residents need not complete and return a publicity release. Winner and companion(s) are responsible for and must possess valid passports, visa and other required travel documentation at time of travel. If a potential winner cannot be contacted after the first attempt to contact him/her or if he/she and their respective travel companion(s) fail to sign and return the affidavits of eligibility and liability/publicity releases within the required time period. An alternate entrant may be selected in his/her place at random from all eligible entries received and the potential winner forfeits the prize. Only two (2) alternate drawings will be held after which the prize will remain unawarded if unclaimed.

Consumer Disclosure

PRIZES. You have not yet won a prize, and no purchase is necessary to win one. Odds of winning any prize are based on the number of eligible entrants during the Contest Period. One (1) Grand Prize winners will be selected and will be awarded two (2) Frontier Airlines Classic flights to be redeemed to any Frontier Airlines destination in the 48 contiguous United States between December 1, 2009 and December 15, 2010 (blackout dates apply). *The Blackout Dates for 2009 are Dec. 18 - 19, 22 - 23, 26 – 29. 2010: Jan. 1 – 5, 15 -16, and 18; Feb. 12, 13, and 15, March 5-7, 11-14, 20, 21, 25 – 28; April 1 – 5 and 10, 11; May 27 – 29, and 31; June 25 – 27; July 1 – 5, 10,11; Sept. 3, 4, 6; Nov. 18 – 30; Dec. 16 – 31.

Each Grand Prize has an Approximate Retail Value ("ARV") of $500.00. All air travel is subject to all applicable travel restrictions, Blackout Dates and fare restrictions. All expenses and incidental travel needs, including but not limited to, meals, lodging, personal charges at lodging, security fees, taxes, or other expenses or incidentals are the responsibility solely of winner. Travel restrictions, conditions and limitations may apply. Sponsor will not replace any lost or stolen tickets, travel vouchers or certificates. The determination of liability for any federal, state or local taxes that may arise out of the winner's receipt and/or use of any prize, and the payment of any such tax liability, shall be the sole responsibility of the winner. However, should federal, state or local law impose any tax reporting or filing obligations on Sponsor arising out of the winner's participation in the Contest (including the winner's receipt of and/or use of any prize), the winner agrees to timely provide Sponsor with any information that is reasonably needed for Sponsor to comply with any such reporting or filing obligations. The ARV of prizes are subject to price changes in the marketplace based on, among other things, any gap in time between the date the ARV is estimated for purposes of these Official Rules and the date the prize is awarded or redeemed. Prizes cannot be substituted, assigned, transferred, or redeemed for cash, except that Sponsor reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to substitute any listed prize for one of equal or greater value if the designated prize should become unavailable for any reason. Prizes cannot be used in conjunction with any other promotion or offer. No cash or other substitution, assignment or transfer of prize by winners is permitted. Any and all applicable federal, state, and local taxes and all fees and expenses related to acceptance and use of prizes not specifically stated herein are the sole responsibility of the individual prize winner.

AUTHORSHIP OF ENTRIES: All answers to the quiz submitted in connection with the Contest are subject to the Facebook Statement of Rights available at http://www.facebook.com/terms.php?ref=pf .

GENERAL RELEASE. BY PARTICIPATING IN THE CONTEST OR RECEIPT OF ANY PRIZE, ENTRANT AGREES TO RELEASE AND HOLD HARMLESS SPONSOR AND AFFILIATED CONTRIBUTORS (Appssavvy, Inc., Where I've Been), AND EACH OF THEIR RESPECTIVE PARENT COMPANIES, SUBSIDIARIES, OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES AND AGENTS (COLLECTIVELY, THE "RELEASED PARTIES") FROM AND AGAINST ANY CLAIM OR CAUSE OF ACTION ARISING OUT OF PARTICIPATION IN THE CONTEST OR RECEIPT, REDEMPTION OR USE OF ANY PRIZE.

LIMITATIONS OF LIABILITY:   
BY SUBMITTING AN ENTRY, ENTRANT AGREES THAT (1) ANY AND ALL DISPUTES, CLAIMS, AND CAUSES OF ACTION ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE CONTEST, OR ANY PRIZE AWARDED, SHALL BE RESOLVED INDIVIDUALLY WITHOUT RESORT TO ANY FORM OF CLASS ACTION, AND ENTRANT WAIVES HIS OR HER RIGHT TO A JURY TRIAL FOR SUCH DISPUTES, CLAIMS AND CAUSES OF ACTION; (2) UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES WILL ENTRANT BE AWARDED ATTORNEYS FEES, COSTS, PUNITIVE, INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES.

SPONSOR AND ITS AFFILIATES, SUBSIDIARIES, REPRESENTATIVES, CONSULTANTS, CONTRACTORS, LEGAL COUNSEL, ADVERTISING, PUBLIC RELATIONS, PROMOTIONAL, FULFILLMENT AND MARKETING AGENCIES, WEB SITE PROVIDERS, WEB MASTERS, AND ADMINISTRATOR, AND THEIR RESPECTIVE OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, REPRESENTATIVES, AND AGENTS ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE IF ANY PRIZE CANNOT BE AWARDED DUE TO TRAVEL CANCELLATIONS, DELAYS, OR INTERRUPTIONS DUE TO ACTS OF GOD, ACTS OF WAR, NATURAL DISASTERS, WEATHER, OR TERRORISM.

CONSTRUCTION. All issues and questions concerning the construction, validity, interpretation and enforceability of these Official Rules, or the rights and obligations of any entrant and Sponsor, shall be governed by, and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Colorado, without giving effect to any choice or conflict of law rules that would cause the application of the laws of any jurisdiction other than Colorado. The invalidity or unenforceability of any provision of these rules shall not affect the validity or enforceability of any other provision. If any such provision is determined to be invalid or otherwise unenforceable, these rules shall be construed in accordance with their terms as if the valid or enforceable provision was not contained therein.

WARNING: ANY ATTEMPT BY AN ENTRANT OR ANY OTHER INDIVIDUAL TO DELIBERATELY DAMAGE ANY WEB SITE ASSOCIATED WITH THIS CONTEST OR UNDERMINE THE LEGITIMATE OPERATION OF THE CONTEST MAY BE A VIOLATION OF CRIMINAL AND CIVIL LAW, AND, SHOULD SUCH AN ATTEMPT BE MADE, SPONSOR RESERVES THE RIGHT TO PROSECUTE AND SEEK DAMAGES FROM ANY SUCH PERSON TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW. Sponsor's failure to enforce any term of these Official Rules shall not constitute a waiver of that provision. Sponsor reserves the right at its sole discretion to disqualify any individual it finds to be attempting to tamper with or undermine the entry process, the web site, and/or the legitimate operation of the Contest; to violate the Official Rules; or to act in an unsportsmanlike or disruptive manner or with the intent to annoy, abuse, threaten, or harass any other person. If, for any reason, the Contest is not capable of running as planned, including infection by computer virus or bugs, tampering, unauthorized intervention, fraud, technical failures, or any other causes beyond the control of Sponsor, that corrupt or affect the operation, administration, security, fairness, integrity, or proper conduct of this Contest, Sponsor may, in its sole discretion, void any suspect entries and (a) cancel or terminate the Contest (or any portion thereof); (b) modify the Contest or suspend the Contest to address the impairment and then resume the Contest in a manner that best conforms to the spirit of these Official Rules; or (c) award the prize at random from among the eligible, non-suspect entries received up to the time of the impairment.

PUBLICITY. Except where prohibited, participation in the Contest constitutes winner's consent to Sponsor's use of winner's name, likeness, Facebook profile picture, voice, opinions, biographical information, hometown and state for promotional purposes in any media, worldwide, without further payment or consideration. Tennessee residents need not complete and return a publicity release. 

WINNER LIST. The winner's name can be obtained by sending a self-addressed stamped envelope with request for winner information to: “Which Frontier Animal Are You?” Contest Winners List (attn: Marketing): Frontier Airlines, Inc., 7001 Tower Road, Denver, CO 80249. Washington and Vermont residents can omit return postage. Requests must be received by December 31, 2009.

PRIVACY. Sponsor will be collecting personal data about participants online, in accordance with its privacy policy. Please review Sponsor's privacy policy at http://www.frontierairlines.com/frontier/privacy.do. By participating in the Contest, entrants hereby agree to Sponsor's collection and usage of their personal information and acknowledge that they have read and accepted Sponsor's privacy policy.

### Sweepstakes

We may occasionally offer Site visitors an opportunity to participate in a survey, contest or sweepstakes. Information we collect for such a survey, contest, or sweepstakes will be subject to the same protection as the information we generally collect from our users.

### Testimonials and User Feedback

We often receive testimonials and comments from users who have had positive experiences with our Service. We occasionally publish such content. When we publish this content, we will identify our users by their names and/or nicknames and may also indicate their current city.

### International Users - Applicable Law

We collect, process, store, disclose and dispose of personal information that you submit to us in accordance with applicable United States law. Please note that the personal information you submit to our Service will be transferred to the United States to be processed by us in order to provide this Site and its services to you or for such other purposes as set forth in this Privacy Policy. If you are not a resident of the United States, you acknowledge and agree that we may collect and use your personal information, as discussed in this Privacy Policy, outside your resident jurisdiction. In addition, we may store such personal information in the United States, outside your resident jurisdiction. In particular, you are advised that the United States uses a sectoral model of privacy protection that relies on a mix of legislation, governmental regulation and self-regulation. Please be aware that United States law may offer different levels of protection for personal information than may be available in your country.

### Effective Date

This Privacy Policy was produced and posted on April 21, 2008.

### Contact Us

If you have questions or concerns regarding your privacy or security on our Site, feel free to Contact Us by email.
